In the following video, I will illustrate various requirements for my assignment. Please note that I will rely mostly on screen shots of my Canvas site organized into an html presentation. It's easier for me than a live presentation and more closely mimics how I will do other videos for my online class. Let me offer two warnings of things I have not quite gotten to, but intend to fix as soon as possible. The current incarnation of the html presentation does not have alt text for my images, so I will place the alt text beneath the images for now. I also need to use descriptive text for many of my URLs. Let me know if you need these fixed prior to certifying my successful completion of this assignment. To keep this video short, I won't read most of the contents of each slide. In a real class video, I would certainly take the time to do this properly.
Here is what you see when you open my Canvas sandbox site. Notice the organized left-hand course navigation menu. The same page displays my "Start Here" page.
My start here page includes the course learning objectives.
Here are the learning objectives for module 1,
and module 2,
and module 3.
You can find the next three requirements via my gradebook.
Here is my published graded assignment. Notice that I need a descriptive label for the URL listed here. I will fix that as soon as possible.
I created a manual grade column using the "on paper" option.
Here is my five question quiz.
You can find a link to my captioned instructor video on my home page.
You can find my syllabus under (surprise!) the syllabus link. It uses headers to make it easier for screen readers. I have yet to includeuse descriptive labels for all my URLs. I will get this done as soon as possible.
Here is my introduction activity, using the Canvas discussion board.
Here is the first of four criteria for my rubric,
and the second,
and the third,
and the fourth.
Here's a review of everything I covered. Thank you and let me know if I need to address any deficiencies.